你们这周末要是有空
Oh, hey, if you guys are free this weekend,
公司奖给我一晚品酒之夜  一起去啊
I won a night of wine tasting from work.
听起来挺有意思啊
That sounds fun.
为什么科学家不像销售员有免费东西拿呢
How come scientists don't win free stuff like salespeople do?
我们投身科学界不是为了得到东西
'Cause we're not in it for the stuff.
而是为了能泡粉丝
We're in it for the groupies.
我个人呢
Personally,
觉得外在奖励挺有损人格
I find the notion of external rewards demeaning.
我投身科学是为了科学发现所带来的欢乐
I pursue science for the intrinsic joy of discovery.
但你不是总念叨着要赢个诺贝尔奖吗
But you always say that you want to win a Nobel Prize.
我也念叨过不要在我朋友面前吐槽我
I also say don't contradict me in front of my friends,
这你丫怎么就没记得呢
but that you don't remember.
好了  你们想去的话就告诉我
All right, well, let me know if you guys want to go.
我愿意
I would love to.
我就很享受陈酿黑皮诺红酒富有层次的口感
I do enjoy the complexity of an aged Pinot noir.
我相信那红酒一定很搭
I'm sure that would pair nicely
你这份炸鸡块
with your fried nuggets of chicken.
听起来会很棒  我们应该去
Well, it sounds like a nice night. We should go.
又是酒吗
Wine again?
不用了  谢谢
Yeah, no, thank you.
我喜欢传统的享用葡萄方式
I like my grapes the old-fashioned way:
就是果汁盒
in a juice box.
我就要去
Well, I'm going.
我在商场时  你就阻止不了我去按摩
You couldn't stop me from getting a massage at the mall,
现在也别想阻止我
and you're not stopping me now.
我为什么要眼睁睁看我女朋友
I shouldn't have to see my girlfriend
在公共场合被别的男人"上下其手"啊
get groped in public by another man.
我又为什么要眼睁睁看我男朋友
And I shouldn't have to see my boyfriend
坐商场里给小孩玩的小火车啊
riding on a train for children around the mall.
给儿童坐的那种迷你火车吗
The little choo-choo for toddlers?
所以你知道我为什么需要找人按摩了吗
And now you know why I needed the massage.
我们不去
Well, we're out.
妮妮怀孕了  不能喝酒
Bernie can't drink 'cause she's pregnant.
而她会怀孕  是因为我们滚床单了
And she's pregnant because we had sex.
而我们会滚床单是因为...
And we had sex because...
这还用说吗
well, come on.
没事的  你跟他们去吧
It's okay. You should go.
你确定吗
You sure?
当然啦
Of course.
对啊  让她耳根清净  远离"这还用说吗"
Yeah, give her a break from, "Well, come on."
妮妮  看来周六晚是你跟我二人时光了
Well, Bernadette, looks like Saturday night, it's you and me.
我吗  怎么  凭啥
Me? How? Why?
这很有道理啊
Well, it makes perfect sense.
因为你身怀六甲  所以不能喝酒
Because you're an expectant mother, you can't drink alcohol.
我是不喜欢喝
I don't like to.
怀孕不能吃寿司生鱼片
You can't have sushi.
我是不喜欢吃
I don't like to.
怀孕不能进浴缸泡热水澡
You can't go in hot tubs.
而我觉得那是一桶人们的汗水汤
I consider them vats of sweaty people soup.
谢尔顿  我不知道...
Gee, Sheldon, I don't know.
别怕啦
Oh, come on.
过山车  咖啡因  半熟的蛋
Roller coasters, caffeine, runny eggs--
我这辈子一直都在避开这些东西
I've been avoiding these things all my life.
而你现在怀孕了  你不避开这些都不行
And now, because you're pregnant, you have to.
但你们的差别是  她是为世界带来生命
The difference is she's bringing life into the world,
而你是带走生命力
and you suck it out.
我们就试试一起玩吧
I guess we could give it a try.
小姑娘  听过用心派对吧
Well, little lady, you've heard of party hearty;
准备迎接"无心"派对吧
get ready to party hardly.
我猜你现在一定超想来一杯
I bet you'd like a drink right now.
翻译：后宫佳丽三千赛   家有爱宠三只猫
猫王进入倒计时  别扭大菜
你们会介意
Hey, you think it'd be okay
我带克莱尔去参加品酒吗
if I brought Claire to the wine tasting?
-可以啊  我也想见她  -那太好了
- Sure. I'd like to meet her. - Oh, that's great.
我也想带她见见大家好久了
I've been wanting her to meet you guys, too,
感觉这次是个很完美的好时机
so this seems like the perfect opportunity.
但是我不会在场啊
Oh, but I won't be there.
真是无巧不成书啊
Funny how that worked out.
所以这代表艾米丽已经宣告出局了吗
Does this mean Emily's not in the picture anymore?
没有啊  我们还会约会
No, I'm still dating her.
大神为我指点迷津
Okay, help me out.
你是怎么做到脚踏两条船
How are you doing this?
她们知道彼此的存在吗
Do they know about each other?
她们都知道我与她们不是专属的关系
They know that we're not exclusive,
所以我们就彼此不要问太多问题就好
and we just don't ask too many questions.
就像我跟你玩"卡亚战神"卡牌游戏
You know, it's like how I play Warlords of Ka'a with you
而跟法兰克与艾丽西娅玩《远古封印》
and Elder Sign with Frank and Alicia.
法兰克与艾丽西娅是谁啊
Who's Frank and Alicia?
我们相处时间已经够长了
Y... You and I spend a lot of time together.
我们之间就不能有些小秘密吗
Can there be a little mystery between us?
好了
Okay.
线路什么的都接好了  准备好啦
Everything's hooked up. We're ready.
我要为后人们录下这一刻
I am going to record this for posterity.
好了  去吧  就决定是你了
All right, here goes nothing.
还"去吧  就决定是你了"呢
Here goes nothing?
这是我们原型的首次测试
This is the initial test of our prototype.
能不能用词正式大气一点
Can we give it a little more gravitas?
行
Fine.
无限持续陀螺仪导向系统
Preliminary trial of the infinite persistence
初步实验:  第一阶段开始
gyroscopic navigational system: phase one commencing.
可能是你声线的问题
Eh... maybe it's your voice.
我看看能不能找詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯配音吧
I'm gonna see if I can get James Earl Jones to do it in post.
太  太美了
It's... it's-it's beautiful.
其实我看得有点头晕了
Actually, it's making me dizzy.
太好了  原来不止我一个
Good, it's not just me.
您好
Hello.
克莱尔  是我
Hey, Claire.
怎么啦
Hey, what's up?
是这样的
Hi, yeah.
我在想
Um, I was wondering,
如果你周六晚有空
if you're free Saturday night,
我的小伙伴们要一起去品酒之夜
all my friends are going to a wine tasting.
好啊  可以吧
Sure, I guess.
你不觉得我见你的朋友们进展太快就行
If you don't think meeting your friends is too big a step.
为什么这会算进展太快呢
Why would it be too big a step?
不知道啊  我不想事情发展得奇怪
I don't know. I just don't want things to get weird.
没什么好担心的啦
Nothing to worry about.
人生就是不断地认识新的人
People meet people all the time,
怎么会奇怪
and it isn't weird.
我见过歌手邦·乔飞  你可能觉得会很怪
I met Bon Jovi once, which you'd think might be weird.
但结果呢  人家好得不得了
Turns out, total sweetheart.
但我们一直处于顺其自然的状态
Okay, but you and I have been keeping things casual.
所以你会跟朋友介绍我是你的朋友
Uh, will you introduce me as your friend
还是女朋友呢
or as your girlfriend?
万一我喜欢他们
What if I like them
他们不喜欢我怎么办
and they don't like me?
万一他们喜欢我  我不喜欢他们怎么办
What if they like me and I don't like them?
天啊  跟邦·乔维见面都没这么多事儿
Boy, it wasn't this hard with Bon Jovi.
我说"你最摇滚最屌"  他说"谢啦  兄弟"
I said, "You rock," he said, "Thanks, man,"
仅此而已
and that was that.
可以走了吗
Hey, you ready to go?
-等等  -你在干嘛
- Hang on. - What are you doing?
我发现一本品酒的书  后面有香味刮刮卡
Oh, I found a scratch-and-sniff book about wine tasting.
全名为"The Essential Scratch and Sniff Guide to Becoming a Wine Expert"
作者是侍酒大师理查德·贝茨  书后配有一张酒香轮盘
它教人们根据不同的味道去识别葡萄酒
It teaches the different flavor notes to look for.
你真的能闻香知酒吗
You actually smell the wine?
大多时间我只闻到我喷鼻剂的味道
I mostly just smell my nasal spray.
你的鼻炎又发作了吗
Are your sinuses acting up?
打从我幼儿园来了一只兔子就没好过
Since my preschool got a bunny.
你今晚还打算跟伯纳黛特一起过吗
Hey, are you still hanging out with Bernadette tonight?
当然
Yes.
我们要证明不需要酒精
And we're going to prove that we don't need alcohol
也能玩得开心
to enjoy ourselves.
挺适合你俩的
Oh, good for you.
也不需要咖啡因  香烟  寿司
Or caffeine, tobacco, sushi,
软干酪  加工肉类  按摩浴缸
soft cheese, processed meats and Jacuzzis,
这些对肚子里的宝宝都会造成伤害
which can all be harmful to an unborn baby.
泡澡时不能吃蜂蜜火腿  懂了
No HoneyBaked Ham in a hot tub-- got it.
也不能洗泡泡澡
Oh, no bubble baths either.
那会增加尿路感染的风险
They can increase the risk of a urinary tract infection.
好的  好好玩
Okay, have fun.
不能吃箭鱼  大耳马鲛  鲨鱼或方头鱼
Oh, and no swordfish, king mackerel, shark or tilefish,
这些鱼类含汞量高
which are all high in mercury.
我们走了
We're leaving now!
还不能跟接触豚鼠
Oh, and no contact with guinea pigs
仓鼠或它们的粪便
or hamsters or their droppings,
不能碰猫砂盆  不能闻油漆味
uh, no-no cat litter boxes, no paint fumes...
我们走啦  爱你哦  再见
Okay, we're leaving, love you, bye!
条条框框什么的最棒了
Boy, do I love restrictions.
其他人呢
Where is everybody?
我们比他们先到一步
Oh, we're the first ones here.
酷
Cool.
是啊
Yeah.
酷
Cool.
我不记得上一次
You know, I don't remember the last time
咱俩独处是什么时候了
it was just you and me hanging out.
我记得  那是三年前
Oh, I do. It was three years ago.
是啊  我们还说以后要经常聚聚
Oh, yeah, and we said we should do it more often.
然后就是现在了
And-and here we are.
谢尔顿和伯纳黛特在一起呢
So, Sheldon and Bernadette are hanging out.
是啊  他们会聊什么呢
I know. What are they gonna talk about?
我不知道
I don't know.
我是真心不知道啊
I really don't know.
-太好了  -谢天谢地
- Oh, good! - Oh, thank God!
你们俩来很久了吗
You guys been here long?
不  刚到两分钟
No, two minutes.
但的确很久了
But yes.
克莱尔呢
Where's Claire?
她直接来这里找我们
Oh, she's meeting us here.
伙计们  帮我个忙
Hey, guys, do me a favor
不要问太多关于我俩关系的事
and don't ask too many questions about the relationship.
我们现在是顺其自然的状态
We're just keeping it casual.
所以我不该问她  作为你的后宫中的
Oh, so I shouldn't ask her how she feels about being
其中一名妃子  有何感想吗
a member of your harem?
我知道你只是耍嘴皮  但小心遭报应
Yeah, I know you're teasing, but watch out for karma.
佩妮  那不是你的前男友扎克吗
Hey, Penny, isn't that your old boyfriend Zack?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你要过去跟他打招呼吗
Are you gonna say hi to him?
不知道耶
Uh, I don't know.
你犹豫时我问下
Hey, while you decide,
谁床上功夫更了得
who was better in bed:
是龙精虎猛扎克哥  还是气喘小弟莱纳德
big hot Zack or wheezy little Leonard?
现世报  来得快
Neener neener.
我带了气泡苹果汁
I brought sparkling cider.
气泡会让我鼻子发痒
Oh... the bubbles tickle my nose.
我现在就打开好了
I'll just open this now
等我们喝的时候  就没气又好喝了
so it can get nice and flat before we drink it.
你今晚想干点什么呀
So what do you want to do tonight?
我已经都计划好了
Oh, I have quite the evening planned.
我们的欢乐爱胎节  第一个节目是
Our fetus-friendly festival of fun begins
深入观察现代火车的世界
with an in-depth look at the world of model trains,
然后我们把快乐加倍  去探索
and then we'll kick things up a notch and explore
制作吐司的各种不同途径
all the different ways that you can make toast.
吐司不就一种吗
There's more than one?
-你知道法式吐司吗  -知道
- You've heard of French toast? - Yeah.
-肉桂吐司呢  -知道
- Cinnamon toast? - Yeah.
-梅尔巴吐司  -知道
- Melba toast? - Yeah.
你懂我话中的意思了吧
You get where I'm going here?
知道
Yeah.
我闻到了土香
I'm getting an earthy note.
肯定掺杂着一丝木香
Ah, there's definitely some oak.
还有  樱桃香吗
Also, uh, cherries?
我啥也闻不到
I smell nothing.
不是吧  啥味儿都没有吗
Really? Nothing?
全是我鼻喷剂的味道
Just a... whole lot of Afrin.
佩妮
Penny?
扎克  你好啊
Oh. Zack, hi!
你们都记得扎克吧
You guys remember Zack.
-当然  你好啊  兄弟  -你好
- Yeah, hey, buddy. - Hello.
你们俩结婚了吗
Hey, did you two get married?
-是的  -对
- We did. - Yeah, mm-hmm.
是跟对方吗
To each other?
是的
Yes.
酷  因为除了当你跟他分手后
Cool. 'Cause other than when you broke up with him
来跟我约会  然后又跟我分手
and dated me, then broke up with me,
然后在回到他身边之前
and then dated me one more time
再次跟我约会的这些时候
before going back to him,
其余时候我一直很看好你们俩哦
I was always rooting for you two.
多谢赏识
Thanks.
科学世界还好吗
So how's the science world?
你们几个在鼓捣啥呢
What are you guys up to?
我们为我们之前发明的导向系统
W-We've actually been working on a prototype
研发一个原型
for a navigation system we invented.
但怕烦到你  细节方面我们就不说了
But we won't bore you with the details.
开什么玩笑  我爱科学
Are you kidding? I love science.
爱因斯坦  史蒂芬·霍金
Einstein, Stephen Hawking,
迈克·泰森是世界著名职业拳手
奈尔·德葛拉司·泰森是以从事科学传播闻名的美国天文学家
迈克·德葛拉司·泰森
Mike deGrasse Tyson.
迈克·德葛拉司·泰森吗
Mike deGrasse Tyson?
是啊  就是拳手泰森留了小胡子后
Yeah, you know, the boxer who grew a mustache
成为了科学家泰森
and became a scientist.
你们发明了什么
So what's your invention?
我们用量子旋涡
Well, we're using quantum vortices
替换了导向系统中的陀螺仪
to replace gyroscopes in guidance systems.
最酷的是它可以永久性地
What's neat is that they can maintain
保持角动量
angular momentum indefinitely.
角动量
Angular momentum.
我正好也在想这个问题呢
I was wondering about that.
它可以安置在卫星或火箭上
You could put it in a satellite or a rocket,
就可以永久运行
and it'll run forever.
很酷嘛
Cool.
那它可以应用在导弹或者其他武器上吗
Could it be used for missiles and war stuff?
当然可以  但我们发明它不是为了制造武器
Yeah, but we didn't create it for weapons.
我也怀疑军方会不会对
And I doubt the military would be interested
我们这小小的导向系统感兴趣
in our little guidance system.
这玩意能比得上他们现在的技术吗
Is it better than the one they use now?
-好太多了  -甩他们几条街
- A lot! - Way better.
你们这群家伙真的智商超群吗
You sure you guys are smart?
H-O级别的火车是1/87比例的
"H-O" gauge trains are 1/87 scale.
N级别的火车是1/160比例的
"N" gauge are 1/160 scale.
另外还有Z级别的火车
And that brings us to "Z" gauge, at a
它的比例大小为"可随口吞下  别问我怎么知道"
"you could easily swallow it, don't ask how I know,"
1/220
1/220.
抱歉  我还是想问一下
I'm sorry, I have to ask.
我五岁的时候   吞下了一个Z级别的火车头
When I was five, I ingested a "Z" gauge locomotive.
接下来的三天我一直默念着  "顺利出洞
I spent the next three days saying, "I think I can pass it,
顺利出洞  顺利出洞"
I think I can pass it, I think I can pass it."
你为什么这么喜欢火车呢
What is it about trains that you like so much?
这个问题问得好
What an interesting question.
小时候  生活对我来说
When I was a child, life was confusing
无序又复杂  火车则代表了一种秩序
and chaotic for me, and trains represented order.
我可以排列  分类  控制火车
I could line them up, categorize them, control them.
可以说  在这个纷乱的世界中
I guess you could say that
只有火车才能带给我一丝平静
they gave me a sense of calm in a world that didn't.
真有爱  谢尔顿
That's lovely, Sheldon.
除了它们会在你肠道里嚓嘎前进之外
Well... other than when they're chugging through your bowels,
火车真是最棒的了
these things are magic.
我必须承认  从一开始
I have to admit, I've been worried about
我对技术被用到军事用途的事就很担心
the military applications since we started talking about this.
我也是
Me, too.
那你怎么不说出来
Why didn't you say something?
就像我从来不提菊花癌一样
Same reason I don't talk about ass cancer.
这个话题可不怎么愉快
It's not a pleasant topic.
你们不能就此放弃啊
You can't let this stop you.
几乎所有的科学发展都可以
Almost any scientific advancement can be used
应用在破坏性的目的上
for destructive purposes.
没错  就连爱因斯坦的相对论
It's true. Even Einstein's theory of relativity
后来也应用在了核武器的研发上
was later applied to the development of nuclear weapons.
E = mc2
E equals MC squared.
没错
Yeah.
E表示能量  M代表质量
"E" is for energy, "M" for mass,
C表示光速
and "C" for the speed of light.
你怎么懂这个
How do you know that?
莱纳德每次拖延射精时间时就念叨这个
Oh, Leonard mumbles it when he wants sex to last longer.
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
克莱尔  你来了
Hey, Claire. Good, you're here.
各位  这是我朋友克莱尔
Guys, this is my friend Claire.
我们只是顺其自然的交往而已
We're casually dating, and there's no need
请大家不要再问问题
for any further questions about it.
你要来杯酒吗
Would you like a glass of wine?
人家说了不要问
I said no questions!
最后也是同样重要的一点
And last but not least,
我喜欢把这个叫做星球大战吐司
this is one that I like to call Star Wars Toast because...
因为它兼具了"光明"和"黑暗"两面
it has a light side and a dark side.
好了  到了玩《龙与地下城》游戏的时候
All righty, it's time for Dungeons & Dragons!
《龙与地下城》
Dungeons & Dragons.
真是不意外
That sounds about right.
你肯定会喜欢这游戏的
You're gonna enjoy this.
我是专门为你设计的版本
I designed it especially for you.
好  但我只玩一小会就好
Okay, but just for a little bit.
我有预感  一旦你开始玩了
Oh, I have a feeling that once you start,
一定会乐此不疲  根本停不下来
you're not gonna want to or be allowed to stop.
好吧
All right.
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
You bet.
你名叫博纳特克斯
Your name is Bernatrix.
你是一名战士女皇
You are a warrior queen.
你人高马大  美艳绝伦
You're strong, beautiful and tall.
我喜欢人高这个设定
I like the idea of being tall.
我还有好多你肯定喜欢的东西呢
I think you're gonna like a lot of things I have in store.
比如  在这个世界里  只有男人才会怀孕
For example, in this world, only the men get pregnant,
所以你老公正在家苦练不要一笑就尿
so your husband is home trying not to pee when he laughs.
有意思  然后呢
This is getting fun. What's next?
你结束了战斗  又渴又累
You're parched and weary from battle.
你来到了一家酒馆面前
You stand in front of a tavern that serves the coldest,
这里有全世界最好喝最冰的麦芽酒
most delicious ale in all the realm.
我好几个月没喝酒了
Oh, I haven't had a drink in months.
你会怎么做
What do you do?
我如狂风般冲进去  丢下我的宝剑
I storm in, slam my sword down,
说  "小二  给老娘把最烈的麦芽酒
and say, "Barkeep, bring me the strongest ale you have
装在哥布林妖精的头骨里端上来"
and serve it in the skull of a Goblin!"
小二要求查看你的身份证
He wants to see I.D.
克莱尔  我们听了很多关于你的好话呢
So, Claire, we've heard so many wonderful things about you.
真的吗  什么好话
Really? Like what?
大部分都是佩妮听说的
Uh, mostly Penny's heard them.
你过去要加冰块时
Boy, you get some dirty looks over there
会有不少鄙视眼光传来啊
when you ask for ice.
扎克  这是我朋友克莱尔
Zack, this is my friend Claire.
你真漂亮  有对象吗
You're hot. You seeing anybody?
她的对象就是我
Uh, she's seeing me.
那你干嘛说她是你朋友
Why'd you say she's your friend?
我们只是顺其自然而已
We're just keeping it casual.
他为什么只是和你顺其自然  你人挺不错啊
Why is he being casual with you? You seem great.
我也不知道  问他吧
I don't know. Ask him.
你为什么只是和她顺其自然  她人挺不错啊
Why are you being casual with her? She seems great.
也许我们应该退一步
Maybe we should take a step back.
为啥要退一步
Take a step back?
我已经过了迎风尿三丈的年纪了
I'm not a young man anymore.
不  我是说重新考虑一下导向系统的事
No, I mean reevaluate what we're doing with the guidance system.
我马上就要当爸爸了
But I got a baby on the way.
我必须得多赚点钱
I got to make some money.
如果我们不小心引发了世界末日
What good is money gonna do
要那么多钱又能干什么
if we inadvertently bring about Armageddon?
等等  你先打住
Okay, let me stop you right there.
我们清楚知道自己的发明
We absolutely know our invention
不会被用来毁灭世界
will not be used to destroy the world.
怎么知道
How?
因为没人从未来穿越回来
Because no one from the future
追杀我们
has come back to kill us.
真好笑
Very funny.
你有更好的想法吗
You got something better?
并没有
Well, not really.
那不就得了
Okay, then.
天啊  你喝了多少酒啊
Geez, how much wine did you drink?
不多
Not a lot.
只是你不走开  我尿不出来
I just couldn't start until you walked away.
地狱虾猛然冲出温泉
The Hell Prawn lunges out of the hot spring!
你用盾牌将其抵挡
You block it with your shield.
你要出击吗
Do you attack?
它有眼睛吗
Does it have eyes?
三只血红色巨眼  从来不眨一下
Three giant red ones and they never blink.
看得人发毛
It's unsettling.
我刺入中间那只眼
I stab it in the middle eye!
明智之举
Good choice!
致命一击  你的剑
Critical hit! Your sword goes
刺穿它的眼睛  直插进它的小脑子
through its eye into its tiny brain.
它奄奄一息地说
With its final dying gasp, it says,
"你已经将我贬为一堆寿司
"You have reduced me to a pile of sushi.
配上这包酱油  好好享用我吧
Enjoy me with this packet of soy sauce.
这是低钠酱油哦"
It's low sodium."
好的  我会把地狱虾吃掉
Okay, I guess I should eat the Hell Prawn.
你用自己的剑
Using your sword,
做出了华丽的寿司大餐
you prepare a beautiful sushi dinner.
你将身子浸入温泉  享受着温水
You slip into the hot spring and enjoy the warm water
泡着你疼痛的关节
on your aching joints.
你满足地闭上眼睛
As you happily close your eyes,
回味着这不可思议的夜晚
you recall the incredible evening you've had
并发现自己的...
and notice that your...
脚和脚踝  比从前还要纤细
...feet and ankles are smaller than they've ever been.
结束
The end.
今晚比我预想的有趣多了
Wow, this night turned out to be so much more fun than I thought.
欢乐尚未停歇
Oh, the fun doesn't stop.
你还能带满满一包吐司回家呢
You're still going home with a goodie bag full of toast.
谢谢你做的这些
Thank you for this.
自从大家发现我怀孕后
You know, ever since people found out I'm having a baby,
都将我当成孕妇伯纳黛特看待
I feel like I became Pregnant Bernadette.
今晚能暂时放下这包袱  真是太好了
It was nice to take a little break tonight.
我能理解
I can understand that.
自从大家发现我是个天才后
From the moment people realized I was a genius,
我就一直被当作天才谢尔顿
I've been Sheldon the Genius.
不过我从来没想过甩掉这包袱
Although I've never really wanted a break from that,
所以我大概也不理解
so I suppose I don't understand.
这多讽刺
Which is ironic
毕竟我是个天才
'cause, you know, genius.
再次谢谢你
Well, thanks again.
不客气
You're welcome.
你什么时候想摆脱孕妇伯纳黛特这包袱
And any time you need a break from being Bernadette the Pregnant,
战士女皇博纳特克斯随时在此等候
Bernatrix the Warrior Queen is here waiting.
那我就恭敬不如从命了
I might just take you up on that.
提醒你哦
Well, mind you now,
此邀约仅在晚期妊娠前有效
that offer's only good until the third trimester.
我不能冒着我的专座被羊水沾到的风险
I can't risk getting amniotic fluid on my spot.
哥们  你在破坏我和克莱尔的关系
Hey, dude, you're killing me with Claire.
这话什么意思
What are you talking about?
我是说  瞧瞧你
I mean, come on, look at you.
典型美男子
You're classically handsome,
还拥有游泳健将的身材
you've got a swimmer's body.
在你身旁  我就被打回原形了
Next to you, I look like me.
兄弟  我不是故意的
Oh, man, I didn't mean to do that.
不过谢谢你看出了我游泳健将的身材
But I do appreciate you recognizing my swimmer's body.
这是个意外
Which, incidentally,
马可波罗是一个在泳池玩的捉迷藏游戏
一个人当鬼蒙上眼睛去抓其他人
我在基督青年会玩"马可波罗"游戏练出来的
I got from playing Marco Polo at the YMCA.
好吧  帮我个忙
Yeah, okay, just... do me a favor
不要再说克莱尔多棒多好了
and stop talking about how great Claire is.
乐意效劳  我的外国小友人
Anything for you, my little foreign friend.
我得问一句
So, I got to ask,
拉杰会带别的姑娘跟你们玩吗
does Raj bring around other girls?
这个嘛
Uh, you know,
我不经常跟他们一起玩
I-I'm not really around that much.
这事艾米比我可清楚多了
Amy knows much more than I do.
我觉得你没什么可担心的
I don't think you have anything to worry about.
拉杰人很好  过分忠诚
Raj is a terrific guy, loyal to a fault.
对啊  他还没丢掉美国在线的邮箱呢
Yeah. He still has an AOL address.
我懂你的意思
I see what you're saying.
她也没有多好嘛
She's not so great.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他总说傻话
He says crazy things all the time.
不信你看  马可
Uh, watch. Marco.
游戏中鬼会先喊"马克"  躲起来的人就回"波罗"
让鬼由声音来判断其他人躲在哪里
波罗
Polo!
你们在聊什么呢
So, uh, what are you guys talking about?
你朋友们正跟我讲
Your friends were just telling me about
你约会的其他姑娘的事儿呢
all the other girls you're dating.
你们干嘛要这样
Why would you do that?
我特地嘱咐过你们不要说
I specifically asked you not to do that.
我们没说
We didn't.
你刚自己说了
You just did.
看来你们没一个智商超群
Maybe none of you guys are smart.
早
Morning.
酒喝太多了
Ugh. Too much wine.
我昨晚也是吃太多了
Oh, I overdid it myself last night.
我也要来片回魂吐司
Hair of the dog.
宿醉时靠再喝酒缓解痛苦的方法
又被称为喝"回魂酒"
你有没有想过我们的导向系统
Hey, did you ever think about the military applications
被用到军事用途上
for the guidance system?
当然了
Of course.
你心里不会不舒服吗
Does it bother you?
不啊  虽然一开始会
No, it did at first,
然后我跟法兰克与艾丽西娅聊过以后
but then I talked it through with Frank and Alicia, and...
他们真的让我换个新角度看待这件事
...they really helped put things into perspective.
这俩人是谁啊
Who are these people?
莱纳德  朋友就像厕纸
Leonard, friends are like toilet paper.
洗手台下面多备着几卷准没错
It's good to have extras under the sink.